Oliver Otis Howard Papers M091 M091
George J. Mitchell Department of Special Collections & Archives, Bowdoin College Library, Brunswick, Maine 04011
- M91.5: Correspondence, eastern command period, December 1888-November 1894, M91.5; 9.25 linear feet
  - 1889 Sep 01 - 1889 Sep 03 (Box 23, Folder 56)
  - 1889 Sep 04 - 1889 Sep 09 (Box 23, Folder 57)
  - 1889 Sep 10 - 1889 Sep 12 (Box 23, Folder 58)
  - 1889 Sep 13 - 1889 Sep 15 (Box 23, Folder 59)
  - 1889 Sep 16 - 1889 Sep 18 (Box 23, Folder 60)
  - 1889 Sep 19 - 1889 Sep 23 (Box 23, Folder 61)
  - 1889 Sep 24 - 1889 Sep 27 (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - 1889 Sep 28 - 1889 Sep 30 (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - 1889 Oct 01 - 1889 Oct 05 (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - 1889 Oct 06 - 1889 Oct 09 (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - 1889 Oct 10 - 1889 Oct 13 (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - 1889 Oct 14 - 1889 Oct 15 (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - 1889 Oct 16 - 1889 Oct 18 (Box 24, Folder 7)
  - 1889 Oct 19 - 1889 Oct 21 (Box 24, Folder 8)
  - 1889 Oct 22 - 1889 Oct 24 (Box 24, Folder 9)
  - 1889 Oct 25 - 1889 Oct 27 (Box 24, Folder 10)
  - 1889 Oct 28 - 1889 Oct 31 (Box 24, Folder 11)
  - 1889 Nov 01 - 1889 Nov 03 (Box 24, Folder 12)
  - 1889 Nov 04 - 1889 Nov 07 (Box 24, Folder 13)
  - 1889 Nov 08 - 1889 Nov 10 (Box 24, Folder 14)
  - 1889 Nov 11 - 1889 Nov 14 (Box 24, Folder 15)
  - 1889 Nov 15 - 1889 Nov 18 (Box 24, Folder 16)
  - 1889 Nov 19 - 1889 Nov 20 (Box 24, Folder 17)
  - 1889 Nov 21 - 1889 Nov 25 (Box 24, Folder 18)
  - 1889 Nov 26 - 1889 Nov 28 (Box 24, Folder 19)
  - 1889 Nov 29 - 1889 Nov 30 (Box 24, Folder 20)
  - 1889 Dec 01 - 1889 Dec 02 (Box 24, Folder 21)
  - 1889 Dec 03 - 1889 Dec 04 (Box 24, Folder 22)
  - 1889 Dec 05 - 1889 Dec 08 (Box 24, Folder 23)
  - 1889 Dec 09 - 1889 Dec 10 (Box 24, Folder 24)
  - 1889 Dec 11 - 1889 Dec 13 (Box 24, Folder 25)
  - 1889 Dec 14 - 1889 Dec 17 (Box 24, Folder 26)
  - 1889 Dec 18 - 1889 Dec 19 (Box 24, Folder 27)
  - 1889 Dec 20 - 1889 Dec 23 (Box 24, Folder 28)
  - 1889 Dec 24 - 1889 Dec 28 (Box 24, Folder 29)
  - 1889 Dec 29 - 1889 Dec 31 (Box 24, Folder 30)
  - 1890 Jan 01 - 1890 Jan 02 (Box 24, Folder 31)
  - 1890 Jan 03 - 1890 Jan 06 (Box 24, Folder 32)
  - 1890 Jan 07 - 1890 Jan 09 (Box 24, Folder 33)
  - 1890 Jan 10 - 1890 Jan 13 (Box 24, Folder 34)
  - 1890 Jan 14 - 1890 Jan 16 (Box 24, Folder 35)
  - 1890 Jan 17 - 1890 Jan 20 (Box 24, Folder 36)
  - 1890 Jan 21 - 1890 Jan 23 (Box 24, Folder 37)
  - 1890 Jan 24 - 1890 Jan 28 (Box 24, Folder 38)
  - 1890 Jan 29 - 1890 Jan 31 (Box 24, Folder 39)
  - 1890 Feb 01 - 1890 Feb 03 (Box 24, Folder 40)
  - 1890 Feb 04 - 1890 Feb 06 (Box 24, Folder 41)
  - 1890 Feb 07 - 1890 Feb 09 (Box 24, Folder 42)
  - 1890 Feb 10 (Box 24, Folder 43)
  - 1890 Feb 11 - 1890 Feb 12 (Box 24, Folder 44)
  - 1890 Feb 13 - 1890 Feb 16 (Box 24, Folder 45)
  - 1890 Feb 17 - 1890 Feb 18 (Box 24, Folder 46)
  - 1890 Feb 19 - 1890 Feb 20 (Box 24, Folder 47)
  - 1890 Feb 21 - 1890 Feb 28 (Box 24, Folder 48)
  - 1890 Mar 01 - 1890 Mar 02 (Box 24, Folder 49)
  - 1890 Mar 03 (Box 24, Folder 50)
  - 1890 Mar 04 - 1890 Mar 05 (Box 24, Folder 51)
  - 1890 Mar 06 - 1890 Mar 07 (Box 24, Folder 52)
  - 1890 Mar 08 - 1890 Mar 10 (Box 24, Folder 53)
  - 1890 Mar 11 - 1890 Mar 14 (Box 24, Folder 54)
  - 1890 Mar 15 - 1890 Mar 17 (Box 24, Folder 55)
  - 1890 Mar 18 (Box 24, Folder 56)
  - 1890 Mar 19 - 1890 Mar 20 (Box 24, Folder 57)
  - 1890 Mar 21 - 1890 Mar 22 (Box 24, Folder 58)
  - 1890 Mar 23 - 1890 Mar 25 (Box 24, Folder 59)
  - 1890 Mar 26 - 1890 Mar 27 (Box 24, Folder 60)
  - 1890 Mar 28 - 1890 Mar 31 (Box 24, Folder 61)
  - 1890 Apr 01 (Box 24, Folder 62)
  - 1890 Apr 02 - 1890 Apr 03 (Box 24, Folder 63)
  - 1890 Apr 04 - 1890 Apr 06 (Box 24, Folder 64)
  - 1890 Apr 07 (Box 24, Folder 65)
  - 1890 Apr 08 - 1890 Apr 11 (Box 24, Folder 66)
  - 1890 Apr 12 - 1890 Apr 15 (Box 24, Folder 67)
  - 1890 Apr 16 - 1890 Apr 20 (Box 24, Folder 68)
  - 1890 Apr 21 - 1890 Apr 22 (Box 24, Folder 69)
  - 1890 Apr 23 - 1890 Apr 24 (Box 24, Folder 70)
  - 1890 Apr 25 - 1890 Apr 27 (Box 24, Folder 71)
  - 1890 Apr 28 - 1890 Apr 30 (Box 24, Folder 72)
  - 1890 May [undated] (Box 24, Folder 73)
  - 1890 May 01 - 1890 May 02 (Box 24, Folder 74)
  - 1890 May 03 - 1890 May 04 (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - 1890 May 05 - 1890 May 06 (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - 1890 May 07 - 1890 May 09 (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - 1890 May 10 - 1890 May 12 (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - 1890 May 13 - 1890 May 14 (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - 1890 May 15 - 1890 May 16 (Box 25, Folder 6)
  - 1890 May 17 - 1890 May 19 (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - 1890 May 20 - 1890 May 21 (Box 25, Folder 8)
  - 1890 May 22 - 1890 May 24 (Box 25, Folder 9)
  - 1890 May 25 - 1890 May 26 (Box 25, Folder 10)
  - 1890 May 27 - 1890 May 28 (Box 25, Folder 11)
  - 1890 May 29 - 1890 May 31 (Box 25, Folder 12)
  - 1890 Jun [undated] (Box 25, Folder 13)
  - 1890 Jun 01 - 1890 Jun 04 (Box 25, Folder 14)
  - 1890 Jun 05 - 1890 Jun 08 (Box 25, Folder 15)
  - 1890 Jun 09 (Box 25, Folder 16)
  - 1890 Jun 10 - 1890 Jun 11 (Box 25, Folder 17)
  - 1890 Jun 12 - 1890 Jun 14 (Box 25, Folder 18)
  - 1890 Jun 15 - 1890 Jun 18 (Box 25, Folder 19)
  - 1890 Jun 19 - 1890 Jun 23 (Box 25, Folder 20)
  - 1890 Jun 24 (Box 25, Folder 21)
  - 1890 Jun 25 - 1890 Jun 27 (Box 25, Folder 22)
  - 1890 Jun 28 - 1890 Jun 30 (Box 25, Folder 23)
  - 1890 Jul 01 - 1890 Jul 07 (Box 25, Folder 24)
  - 1890 Jul 08 - 1890 Jul 13 (Box 25, Folder 25)
  - 1890 Jul 14 - 1890 Jul 18 (Box 25, Folder 26)
  - 1890 Jul 19 - 1890 Jul 21 (Box 25, Folder 27)
  - 1890 Jul 22 - 1890 Jul 24 (Box 25, Folder 28)
  - 1890 Jul 25 - 1890 Jul 31 (Box 25, Folder 29)
  - 1890 Aug 01 - 1890 Aug 05 (Box 25, Folder 30)
  - 1890 Aug 06 - 1890 Aug 08 (Box 25, Folder 31)
  - 1890 Aug 09 - 1890 Aug 13 (Box 25, Folder 32)
  - 1890 Aug 14 - 1890 Aug 19 (Box 25, Folder 33)
  - 1890 Aug 20 - 1890 Aug 25 (Box 25, Folder 34)
  - 1890 Aug 26 - 1890 Aug 31 (Box 25, Folder 35)
  - 1890 Sep 01 - 1890 Sep 04 (Box 25, Folder 36)
  - 1890 Sep 05 - 1890 Sep 08 (Box 25, Folder 37)
  - 1890 Sep 09 - 1890 Sep 11 (Box 25, Folder 38)
  - 1890 Sep 12 - 1890 Sep 15 (Box 25, Folder 39)
  - 1890 Sep 16 - 1890 Sep 20 (Box 25, Folder 40)
  - 1890 Sep 21 - 1890 Sep 24 (Box 25, Folder 41)
  - 1890 Sep 25 - 1890 Sep 28 (Box 25, Folder 42)
  - 1890 Sep 29 - 1890 Sep 30 (Box 25, Folder 43)
  - 1890 Oct 01 - 1890 Oct 03 (Box 25, Folder 44)
  - 1890 Oct 04 - 1890 Oct 06 (Box 25, Folder 45)
  - 1890 Oct 07 - 1890 Oct 14 (Box 25, Folder 46)
  - 1890 Oct 15 - 1890 Oct 22 (Box 25, Folder 47)
  - 1890 Oct 23 - 1890 Oct 26 (Box 25, Folder 48)
  - 1890 Oct 27 - 1890 Oct 31 (Box 25, Folder 49)
  - 1890 Nov 01 - 1890 Nov 02 (Box 25, Folder 50)
  - 1890 Nov 03 - 1890 Nov 04 (Box 25, Folder 51)
  - 1890 Nov 05 - 1890 Nov 06 (Box 25, Folder 52)
  - 1890 Nov 07 - 1890 Nov 08 (Box 25, Folder 53)
  - 1890 Nov 09 - 1890 Nov 11 (Box 25, Folder 54)
  - 1890 Nov 12 - 1890 Nov 13 (Box 25, Folder 55)
  - 1890 Nov 14 - 1890 Nov 16 (Box 25, Folder 56)
  - 1890 Nov 17 (Box 25, Folder 57)
  - 1890 Nov 18 - 1890 Nov 20 (Box 25, Folder 58)
  - 1890 Nov 21 - 1890 Nov 22 (Box 25, Folder 59)
  - 1890 Nov 23 - 1890 Nov 25 (Box 25, Folder 60)
  - 1890 Nov 26 (Box 25, Folder 61)
  - 1890 Nov 27 - 1890 Nov 30 (Box 25, Folder 62)
  - 1890 Dec 01 - 1890 Dec 03 (Box 25, Folder 63)
  - 1890 Dec 04 - 1890 Dec 06 (Box 25, Folder 64)
  - 1890 Dec 07 - 1890 Dec 10 (Box 25, Folder 65)
  - 1890 Dec 11 - 1890 Dec 15 (Box 25, Folder 66)
  - 1890 Dec 16 - 1890 Dec 19 (Box 25, Folder 67)
  - 1890 Dec 20 - 1890 Dec 22 (Box 25, Folder 68)
  - 1890 Dec 23 - 1890 Dec 25 (Box 25, Folder 69)
  - 1890 Dec 26 - 1890 Dec 31 (Box 25, Folder 70)
  - 1891 Jan 01 - 1890 Jan 05 (Box 25, Folder 71)
  - 1891 Jan 06 - 1891 Jan 09 (Box 25, Folder 72)
  - 1891 Jan 10 - 1891 Jan 13 (Box 25, Folder 73)
  - 1891 Jan 14 - 1891 Jan 17 (Box 25, Folder 74)
  - 1891 Jan 18 - 1891 Jan 20 (Box 25, Folder 75)
  - 1891 Jan 21 - 1891 Jan 22 (Box 25, Folder 76)
  - 1891 Jan 23 - 1891 Jan 24 (Box 25, Folder 77)
  - 1891 Jan 25 - 1891 Jan 31 (Box 25, Folder 78)
  - 1891 Feb 01 - 1891 Feb 02 (Box 25, Folder 79)
  - 1891 Feb 03 - 1891 Feb 07 (Box 25, Folder 80)
  - 1891 Feb 08 - 1891 Feb 11 (Box 25, Folder 81)
  - 1891 Feb 12 - 1891 Feb 15 (Box 25, Folder 82)
  - 1891 Feb 16 (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - 1891 Feb 17 - 1891 Feb 18 (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - 1891 Feb 19 - 1891 Feb 20 (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - 1891 Feb 21 - 1891 Feb 24 (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - 1891 Feb 25 - 1891 Feb 26 (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - 1891 Feb 27 - 1891 Feb 28 (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - 1891 Mar 01 (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - 1891 Mar 02 - 1891 Mar 04 (Box 26, Folder 8)
  - 1891 Mar 05 - 1891 Mar 06 (Box 26, Folder 9)
  - 1891 Mar 07 - 1891 Mar 09 (Box 26, Folder 10)
  - 1891 Mar 10 - 1891 Mar 11 (Box 26, Folder 11)
  - 1891 Mar 12 - 1891 Mar 16 (Box 26, Folder 12)
  - 1891 Mar 17 - 1891 Mar 19 (Box 26, Folder 13)
  - 1891 Mar 20 - 1891 Mar 22 (Box 26, Folder 14)
  - 1891 Mar 23 - 1891 Mar 25 (Box 26, Folder 15)
  - 1891 Mar 26 - 1891 Mar 27 (Box 26, Folder 16)
  - 1891 Mar 28 - 1891 Mar 31 (Box 26, Folder 17)
  - 1891 Apr 01 (Box 26, Folder 18)
  - 1891 Apr 02 - 1891 Apr 03 (Box 26, Folder 19)
  - 1891 Apr 04 - 1891 Apr 05 (Box 26, Folder 20)
  - 1891 Apr 06 - 1891 Apr 08 (Box 26, Folder 21)
  - 1891 Apr 09 - 1891 Apr 12 (Box 26, Folder 22)
  - 1891 Apr 13 - 1891 Apr 14 (Box 26, Folder 23)
  - 1891 Apr 15 - 1891 Apr 17 (Box 26, Folder 24)
  - 1891 Apr 18 - 1891 Apr 21 (Box 26, Folder 25)
  - 1891 Apr 22 - 1891 Apr 24 (Box 26, Folder 26)
  - 1891 Apr 25 - 1891 Apr 28 (Box 26, Folder 27)
  - 1891 Apr 29 - 1891 Apr 30 (Box 26, Folder 28)
  - 1891 May 01 - 1891 May 04 (Box 26, Folder 29)
  - 1891 May 05 - 1891 May 07 (Box 26, Folder 30)
  - 1891 May 08 - 1891 May 10 (Box 26, Folder 31)
  - 1891 May 11 - 1891 May 13 (Box 26, Folder 32)
  - 1891 May 14 - 1891 May 15 (Box 26, Folder 33)
  - 1891 May 16 - 1891 May 19 (Box 26, Folder 34)
  - 1891 May 20 - 1891 May 23 (Box 26, Folder 35)
  - 1891 May 24 - 1891 May 26 (Box 26, Folder 36)
  - 1891 May 27 - 1891 May 31 (Box 26, Folder 37)
  - 1891 Jun 01 - 1891 Jun 02 (Box 26, Folder 38)
  - 1891 Jun 03 - 1891 Jun 07 (Box 26, Folder 39)
  - 1891 Jun 08 - 1891 Jun 11 (Box 26, Folder 40)
  - 1891 Jun 12 - 1891 Jun 14 (Box 26, Folder 41)
  - 1891 Jun 15 - 1891 Jun 19 (Box 26, Folder 42)
  - 1891 Jun 20 - 1891 Jun 22 (Box 26, Folder 43)
  - 1891 Jun 23 - 1891 Jun 26 (Box 26, Folder 44)
  - 1891 Jun 27 - 1891 Jun 30 (Box 26, Folder 45)
  - 1891 Jul 01 - 1891 Jul 05 (Box 26, Folder 46)
  - 1891 Jul 06 - 1891 Jul 07 (Box 26, Folder 47)
  - 1891 Jul 08 - 1891 Jul 10 (Box 26, Folder 48)
  - 1891 Jul 11 - 1891 Jul 14 (Box 26, Folder 49)
  - 1891 Jul 15 - 1891 Jul 20 (Box 26, Folder 50)
  - 1891 Jul 21 - 1891 Jul 23 (Box 26, Folder 51)
  - 1891 Jul 24 - 1891 Jul 31 (Box 26, Folder 52)
  - 1891 Aug 01 - 1891 Aug 06 (Box 26, Folder 53)
  - 1891 Aug 07 - 1891 Aug 12 (Box 26, Folder 54)
  - 1891 Aug 13 - 1891 Aug 18 (Box 26, Folder 55)
  - 1891 Aug 19 - 1891 Aug 31 (Box 26, Folder 56)
  - 1891 Sep 01 - 1891 Sep 05 (Box 26, Folder 57)
  - 1891 Sep 06 - 1891 Sep 10 (Box 26, Folder 58)
  - 1891 Sep 11 - 1891 Sep 15 (Box 26, Folder 59)
  - 1891 Sep 16 - 1891 Sep 19 (Box 26, Folder 60)
  - 1891 Sep 20 - 1891 Sep 24 (Box 26, Folder 61)
  - 1891 Sep 25 - 1891 Sep 28 (Box 26, Folder 62)
  - 1891 Sep 29 - 1891 Sep 30 (Box 26, Folder 63)
  - 1891 Oct 01 - 1891 Oct 03 (Box 26, Folder 64)
  - 1891 Oct 04 - 1891 Oct 08 (Box 26, Folder 65)
  - 1891 Oct 09 - 1891 Oct 12 (Box 26, Folder 66)
  - 1891 Oct 13 - 1891 Oct 15 (Box 26, Folder 67)
  - 1891 Oct 16 - 1891 Oct 19 (Box 26, Folder 68)
  - 1891 Oct 20 - 1891 Oct 23 (Box 26, Folder 69)
  - 1891 Oct 24 - 1891 Oct 31 (Box 26, Folder 70)
  - 1891 Nov 01 - 1891 Nov 03 (Box 26, Folder 71)
  - 1891 Nov 04 - 1891 Nov 05 (Box 26, Folder 72)
  - 1891 Nov 06 - 1891 Nov 08 (Box 26, Folder 73)
  - 1891 Nov 09 - 1891 Nov 11 (Box 26, Folder 74)
  - 1891 Nov 12 - 1891 Nov 15 (Box 26, Folder 75)
  - 1891 Nov 16 - 1891 Nov 18 (Box 26, Folder 76)
  - 1891 Nov 19 - 1891 Nov 22 (Box 26, Folder 77)
  - 1891 Nov 23 - 1891 Nov 27 (Box 26, Folder 78)
  - 1891 Nov 28 - 1891 Nov 31 (Box 26, Folder 79)
  - 1891 Dec 01 - 1891 Dec 02 (Box 26, Folder 80)
  - 1891 Dec 03 - 1891 Dec 04 (Box 26, Folder 81)
  - 1891 Dec 05 - 1891 Dec 10 (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - 1891 Dec 11 - 1891 Dec 16 (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - 1891 Dec 17 - 1891 Dec 19 (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - 1891 Dec 20 - 1891 Dec 22 (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - 1891 Dec 23 - 1891 Dec 26 (Box 27, Folder 5)
  - 1891 Dec 27 - 1891 Dec 30 (Box 27, Folder 6)
  - 1891 Dec 31 (Box 27, Folder 7)
  - 1892 Jan 01 - 1892 Jan 04 (Box 27, Folder 8)
  - 1892 Jan 05 - 1892 Jan 06 (Box 27, Folder 9)
  - 1892 Jan 07 - 1892 Jan 09 (Box 27, Folder 10)
  - 1892 Jan 10 - 1892 Jan 13 (Box 27, Folder 11)
  - 1892 Jan 14 - 1892 Jan 16 (Box 27, Folder 12)
  - 1892 Jan 17 - 1892 Jan 20 (Box 27, Folder 13)
  - 1892 Jan 21 - 1892 Jan 22 (Box 27, Folder 14)
  - 1892 Jan 23 - 1892 Jan 24 (Box 27, Folder 15)
  - 1892 Jan 25 - 1892 Jan 26 (Box 27, Folder 16)
  - 1892 Jan 27 (Box 27, Folder 17)
  - 1892 Jan 28 (Box 27, Folder 18)
  - 1892 Jan 29 - 1892 Jan 31 (Box 27, Folder 19)
  - 1892 Feb 01 - 1892 Feb 02 (Box 27, Folder 20)
  - 1892 Feb 03 - 1892 Feb 04 (Box 27, Folder 21)
  - 1892 Feb 05 - 1892 Feb 06 (Box 27, Folder 22)
  - 1892 Feb 07 - 1892 Feb 08 (Box 27, Folder 23)
  - 1892 Feb 09 - 1892 Feb 10 (Box 27, Folder 24)
  - 1892 Feb 11 - 1892 Feb 12 (Box 27, Folder 25)
  - 1892 Feb 13 - 1892 Feb 15 (Box 27, Folder 26)
  - 1892 Feb 16 - 1892 Feb 17 (Box 27, Folder 27)
  - 1892 Feb 18 - 1892 Feb 20 (Box 27, Folder 28)
  - 1892 Feb 21 - 1892 Feb 23 (Box 27, Folder 29)
  - 1892 Feb 24 - 1892 Feb 26 (Box 27, Folder 30)
  - 1892 Feb 27 - 1892 Feb 29 (Box 27, Folder 31)
  - 1892 Mar 01 - 1892 Mar 04 (Box 27, Folder 32)
  - 1892 Mar 05 - 1892 Mar 07 (Box 27, Folder 33)
  - 1892 Mar 08 - 1892 Mar 10 (Box 27, Folder 34)
  - 1892 Mar 11 - 1892 Mar 16 (Box 27, Folder 35)
  - 1892 Mar 17 - 1892 Mar 22 (Box 27, Folder 36)
  - 1892 Mar 23 - 1892 Mar 25 (Box 27, Folder 37)
  - 1892 Mar 26 - 1892 Mar 31 (Box 27, Folder 38)
  - 1892 Apr 01 - 1892 Apr 03 (Box 27, Folder 39)
  - 1892 Apr 04 - 1892 Apr 06 (Box 27, Folder 40)
  - 1892 Apr 07 - 1892 Apr 08 (Box 27, Folder 41)
  - 1892 Apr 09 - 1892 Apr 11 (Box 27, Folder 42)
  - 1892 Apr 12 - 1892 Apr 14 (Box 27, Folder 43)
  - 1892 Apr 15 - 1892 Apr 17 (Box 27, Folder 44)
  - 1892 Apr 18 - 1892 Apr 20 (Box 27, Folder 45)
  - 1892 Apr 21 - 1892 Apr 27 (Box 27, Folder 46)
  - 1892 Apr 28 - 1892 Apr 30 (Box 27, Folder 47)
  - 1892 May 01 (Box 27, Folder 48)
  - 1892 May 02 (Box 27, Folder 49)
  - 1892 May 03 (Box 27, Folder 50)
  - 1892 May 04 - 1892 May 05 (Box 27, Folder 51)
  - 1892 May 06 - 1892 May 07 (Box 27, Folder 52)
  - 1892 May 09 - 1892 May 10 (Box 27, Folder 53)
  - 1892 May 11 (Box 27, Folder 54)
  - 1892 May 12 (Box 27, Folder 55)
  - 1892 May 13 - 1892 May 14 (Box 27, Folder 56)
  - 1892 May 15 - 1892 May 16 (Box 27, Folder 57)
  - 1892 May 17 - 1892 May 18 (Box 27, Folder 58)
  - 1892 May 19 (Box 27, Folder 59)
  - 1892 May 20 (Box 27, Folder 60)
  - 1892 May 21 - 1892 May 22 (Box 27, Folder 61)
  - 1892 May 23 (Box 27, Folder 62)
  - 1892 May 24 (Box 27, Folder 63)
  - 1892 May 25 - 1892 May 26 (Box 27, Folder 64)
  - 1892 May 27 (Box 27, Folder 65)
  - 1892 May 28 - 1892 May 31 (Box 27, Folder 66)
  - 1892 Jun 01 (Box 27, Folder 67)
  - 1892 Jun 02 - 1892 Jun 03 (Box 27, Folder 68)
  - 1892 Jun 04 - 1892 Jun 05 (Box 27, Folder 69)
  - 1892 Jun 06 - 1892 Jun 07 (Box 27, Folder 70)
  - 1892 Jun 08 - 1892 Jun 10 (Box 27, Folder 71)
  - 1892 Jun 11 - 1892 Jun 15 (Box 27, Folder 72)
  - 1892 Jun 16 - 1892 Jun 20 (Box 27, Folder 73)
  - 1892 Jun 21 - 1892 Jun 23 (Box 27, Folder 74)
  - 1892 Jun 24 - 1892 Jun 30 (Box 27, Folder 75)
  - 1892 Jul 01 - 1892 Jul 05 (Box 27, Folder 76)
  - 1892 Jul 06 - 1892 Jul 07 (Box 27, Folder 77)
  - 1892 Jul 08 - 1892 Jul 12 (Box 27, Folder 78)
  - 1892 Jul 13 - 1892 Jul 18 (Box 27, Folder 79)
  - 1892 Jul 19 - 1892 Jul 22 (Box 27, Folder 80)
  - 1892 Jul 23 - 1892 Jul 26 (Box 27, Folder 81)
  - 1892 Jul 27 - 1892 Jul 31 (Box 27, Folder 82)
  - 1892 Aug 01 - 1892 Aug 04 (Box 27, Folder 83)
  - 1892 Aug 05 - 1892 Aug 10 (Box 27, Folder 84)
  - 1892 Aug 11 - 1892 Aug 17 (Box 28, Folder 1)
  - 1892 Aug 18 - 1892 Aug 23 (Box 28, Folder 2)
  - 1892 Aug 24 - 1892 Aug 27 (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - 1892 Aug 28 - 1892 Aug 31 (Box 28, Folder 4)
  - 1892 Sep 01 - 1892 Aug 06 (Box 28, Folder 5)
  - 1892 Sep 07 - 1892 Sep 09 (Box 28, Folder 6)
  - 1892 Sep 10 - 1892 Sep 14 (Box 28, Folder 7)
  - 1892 Sep 15 - 1892 Sep 17 (Box 28, Folder 8)
  - 1892 Sep 18 - 1892 Sep 22 (Box 28, Folder 9)
  - 1892 Sep 23 - 1892 Sep 26 (Box 28, Folder 10)
  - 1892 Sep 27 - 1892 Sep 28 (Box 28, Folder 11)
  - 1892 Sep 29 - 1892 Sep 30 (Box 28, Folder 12)
  - 1892 Oct 01 - 1892 Oct 05 (Box 28, Folder 13)
  - 1892 Oct 06 - 1892 Oct 09 (Box 28, Folder 14)
  - 1892 Oct 10 - 1892 Oct 13 (Box 28, Folder 15)
  - 1892 Oct 14 - 1892 Oct 20 (Box 28, Folder 16)
  - 1892 Oct 20 - 1892 Oct 31 (Box 28, Folder 17)
  - 1892 Nov 01 - 1892 Nov 13 (Box 28, Folder 18)
  - 1892 Nov 14 - 1892 Nov 24 (Box 28, Folder 19)
  - 1892 Nov 25 - 1892 Nov 31 (Box 28, Folder 20)
  - 1892 Dec 01 - 1892 Dec 08 (Box 28, Folder 21)
  - 1892 Dec 09 - 1892 Dec 13 (Box 28, Folder 22)
  - 1892 Dec 14 - 1892 Dec 17 (Box 28, Folder 23)
  - 1892 Dec 18 - 1892 Dec 22 (Box 28, Folder 24)
  - 1892 Dec 23 - 1892 Dec 27 (Box 28, Folder 25)
  - 1892 Dec 28 - 1892 Dec 30 (Box 28, Folder 26)
  - 1892 Dec 31 (Box 28, Folder 27)
  - 1893 Jan 01 - 1893 Jan 03 (Box 28, Folder 28)
  - 1893 Jan 04 - 1893 Jan 05 (Box 28, Folder 29)
  - 1893 Jan 06 - 1893 Jan 09 (Box 28, Folder 30)
  - 1893 Jan 10 - 1893 Jan 11 (Box 28, Folder 31)
  - 1893 Jan 12 - 1893 Jan 13 (Box 28, Folder 32)
  - 1893 Jan 14 - 1893 Jan 16 (Box 28, Folder 33)
  - 1893 Jan 17 - 1893 Jan 19 (Box 28, Folder 34)
  - 1893 Jan 20 - 1893 Jan 23 (Box 28, Folder 35)
  - 1893 Jan 24 - 1893 Jan 26 (Box 28, Folder 36)
  - 1893 Jan 27 - 1893 Jan 31 (Box 28, Folder 37)
  - 1893 Feb 01 - 1893 Jan 04 (Box 28, Folder 38)
  - 1893 Feb 05 - 1893 Feb 07 (Box 28, Folder 39)
  - 1893 Feb 08 - 1893 Feb 10 (Box 28, Folder 40)
  - 1893 Feb 11 - 1893 Feb 15 (Box 28, Folder 41)
  - 1893 Feb 16 - 1893 Feb 17 (Box 28, Folder 42)
  - 1893 Feb 18 - 1893 Feb 21 (Box 28, Folder 43)
  - 1893 Feb 22 - 1893 Feb 23 (Box 28, Folder 44)
  - 1893 Feb 24 - 1893 Feb 27 (Box 28, Folder 45)
  - 1893 Feb 28 (Box 28, Folder 46)
  - 1893 Mar 01 - 1893 Feb 05 (Box 28, Folder 47)
  - 1893 Mar 06 - 1893 Mar 09 (Box 28, Folder 48)
  - 1893 Mar 10 - 1893 Mar 13 (Box 28, Folder 49)
  - 1893 Mar 14 - 1893 Mar 17 (Box 28, Folder 50)
  - 1893 Mar 18 - 1893 Mar 21 (Box 28, Folder 51)
  - 1893 Mar 22 - 1893 Mar 26 (Box 28, Folder 52)
  - 1893 Mar 27 - 1893 Mar 31 (Box 28, Folder 53)
  - 1893 Apr 01 - 1893 Apr 05 (Box 28, Folder 54)
  - 1893 Apr 06 - 1893 Apr 11 (Box 28, Folder 55)
  - 1893 Apr 12 - 1893 Apr 15 (Box 28, Folder 56)
  - 1893 Apr 16 - 1893 Apr 18 (Box 28, Folder 57)
  - 1893 Apr 19 - 1893 Apr 20 (Box 28, Folder 58)
  - 1893 Apr 21 - 1893 Apr 22 (Box 28, Folder 59)
  - 1893 Apr 23 - 1893 Apr 24 (Box 28, Folder 60)
  - 1893 Apr 25 - 1893 Apr 28 (Box 28, Folder 61)
  - 1893 Apr 29 - 1893 Apr 30 (Box 28, Folder 62)
  - 1893 May 01 - 1893 May 03 (Box 28, Folder 63)
  - 1893 May 04 - 1893 May 06 (Box 28, Folder 64)
  - 1893 May 07 - 1893 May 09 (Box 28, Folder 65)
  - 1893 May 10 - 1893 May 12 (Box 28, Folder 66)
  - 1893 May 13 - 1893 May 15 (Box 28, Folder 67)
  - 1893 May 16 - 1893 May 17 (Box 28, Folder 68)
  - 1893 May 18 - 1893 May 20 (Box 28, Folder 69)
  - 1893 May 21 - 1893 May 23 (Box 28, Folder 70)
  - 1893 May 24 - 1893 May 28 (Box 28, Folder 71)
  - 1893 May 29 - 1893 May 31 (Box 28, Folder 72)
  - 1893 Jun 01 - 1893 Jun 04 (Box 28, Folder 73)
  - 1893 Jun 05 - 1893 Jun 06 (Box 28, Folder 74)
  - 1893 Jun 07 - 1893 Jun 08 (Box 28, Folder 75)
  - 1893 Jun 09 - 1893 Jun 12 (Box 28, Folder 76)
  - 1893 Jun 13 - 1893 Jun 15 (Box 28, Folder 77)
  - 1893 Jun 16 - 1893 Jun 20 (Box 28, Folder 78)
  - 1893 Jun 21 - 1893 Jun 23 (Box 28, Folder 79)
  - 1893 Jun 25 - 1893 Jun 28 (Box 28, Folder 80)
  - 1893 Jun 29 - 1893 Jun 30 (Box 28, Folder 81)
  - 1893 Jul 01 - 1893 Jul 04 (Box 28, Folder 82)
  - 1893 Jul 05 - 1893 Jul 09 (Box 29, Folder 1)
  - 1893 Jul 10 - 1893 Jul 13 (Box 29, Folder 2)
  - 1893 Jul 14 - 1893 Jul 18 (Box 29, Folder 3)
  - 1893 Jul 19 - 1893 Jul 22 (Box 29, Folder 4)
  - 1893 Jul 24 - 1893 Jul 31 (Box 29, Folder 5)
  - 1893 Aug 01 - 1893 Aug 03 (Box 29, Folder 6)
  - 1893 Aug 04 - 1893 Aug 07 (Box 29, Folder 7)
  - 1893 Aug 08 - 1893 Aug 12 (Box 29, Folder 8)
  - 1893 Aug 14 - 1893 Aug 16 (Box 29, Folder 9)
  - 1893 Aug 17 - 1893 Aug 19 (Box 29, Folder 10)
  - 1893 Aug 22 - 1893 Aug 25 (Box 29, Folder 11)
  - 1893 Aug 26 - 1893 Aug 31 (Box 29, Folder 12)
  - 1893 Sep 01 - 1893 Sep 03 (Box 29, Folder 13)
  - 1893 Sep 04 - 1893 Sep 06 (Box 29, Folder 14)
  - 1893 Sep 07 - 1893 Sep 08 (Box 29, Folder 15)
  - 1893 Sep 09 - 1893 Sep 12 (Box 29, Folder 16)
  - 1893 Sep 13 - 1893 Sep 15 (Box 29, Folder 17)
  - 1893 Sep 16 - 1893 Sep 18 (Box 29, Folder 18)
  - 1893 Sep 19 - 1893 Sep 23 (Box 29, Folder 19)
  - 1893 Sep 24 - 1893 Sep 28 (Box 29, Folder 20)
  - 1893 Sep 29 - 1893 Sep 30 (Box 29, Folder 21)
  - 1893 Oct 01 - 1893 Oct 04 (Box 29, Folder 22)
  - 1893 Oct 05 - 1893 Oct 10 (Box 29, Folder 23)
  - 1893 Oct 11 - 1893 Oct 15 (Box 29, Folder 24)
  - 1893 Oct 16 - 1893 Oct 17 (Box 29, Folder 25)
  - 1893 Oct 18 - 1893 Oct 19 (Box 29, Folder 26)
  - 1893 Oct 20 - 1893 Oct 22 (Box 29, Folder 27)
  - 1893 Oct 23 - 1893 Oct 24 (Box 29, Folder 28)
  - 1893 Oct 25 - 1893 Oct 26 (Box 29, Folder 29)
  - 1893 Oct 27 - 1893 Oct 31 (Box 29, Folder 30)
  - 1893 Nov 01 - 1893 Nov 03 (Box 29, Folder 31)
  - 1893 Nov 04 - 1893 Nov 07 (Box 29, Folder 32)
  - 1893 Nov 08 - 1893 Nov 10 (Box 29, Folder 33)
  - 1893 Nov 12 - 1893 Nov 14 (Box 29, Folder 34)
  - 1893 Nov 15 - 1893 Nov 19 (Box 29, Folder 35)
  - 1893 Nov 20 - 1893 Nov 21 (Box 29, Folder 36)
  - 1893 Nov 22 - 1893 Nov 23 (Box 29, Folder 37)
  - 1893 Nov 24 - 1893 Nov 26 (Box 29, Folder 38)
  - 1893 Nov 27 - 1893 Nov 28 (Box 29, Folder 39)
  - 1893 Nov 29 - 1893 Nov 31 (Box 29, Folder 40)
  - 1893 Dec 01 - 1893 Dec 03 (Box 29, Folder 41)
  - 1893 Dec 04 - 1893 Dec 06 (Box 29, Folder 42)
  - 1893 Dec 07 - 1893 Dec 08 (Box 29, Folder 43)
  - 1893 Dec 09 - 1893 Dec 11 (Box 29, Folder 44)
  - 1893 Dec 12 - 1893 Dec 13 (Box 29, Folder 45)
  - 1893 Dec 14 - 1893 Dec 17 (Box 29, Folder 46)
  - 1893 Dec 18 - 1893 Dec 19 (Box 29, Folder 47)
  - 1893 Dec 20 - 1893 Dec 23 (Box 29, Folder 48)
  - 1893 Dec 25 - 1893 Dec 31 (Box 29, Folder 49)
  - 1894 Jan 01 - 1894 Jan 02 (Box 29, Folder 50)
  - 1894 Jan 03 - 1894 Jan 05 (Box 29, Folder 51)
  - 1894 Jan 06 - 1894 Jan 08 (Box 29, Folder 52)
  - 1894 Jan 09 - 1894 Jan 10 (Box 29, Folder 53)
  - 1894 Jan 11 - 1894 Jan 12 (Box 29, Folder 54)
  - 1894 Jan 13 - 1894 Jan 15 (Box 29, Folder 55)
  - 1894 Jan 16 - 1894 Jan 18 (Box 29, Folder 56)
  - 1894 Jan 19 - 1894 Jan 21 (Box 29, Folder 57)
  - 1894 Jan 22 - 1894 Jan 23 (Box 29, Folder 58)
  - 1894 Jan 24 - 1894 Jan 27 (Box 29, Folder 59)
  - 1894 Jan 28 - 1894 Jan 31 (Box 29, Folder 60)
  - 1894 Feb 01 - 1894 Feb 04 (Box 29, Folder 61)
  - 1894 Feb 05 - 1894 Feb 06 (Box 29, Folder 62)
  - 1894 Feb 07 - 1894 Feb 09 (Box 29, Folder 63)
  - 1894 Feb 10 - 1894 Feb 12 (Box 29, Folder 64)
  - 1894 Feb 13 - 1894 Feb 14 (Box 29, Folder 65)
  - 1894 Feb 15 (Box 29, Folder 66)
  - 1894 Feb 16 - 1894 Feb 17 (Box 29, Folder 67)
  - 1894 Feb 18 - 1894 Feb 20 (Box 29, Folder 68)
  - 1894 Feb 21 - 1894 Feb 22 (Box 29, Folder 69)
  - 1894 Feb 23 - 1894 Feb 24 (Box 30, Folder 1)
  - 1894 Feb 25 - 1894 Feb 27 (Box 30, Folder 2)
  - 1894 Feb 28 (Box 30, Folder 3)
  - 1894 Mar 01 (Box 30, Folder 4)
  - 1894 Mar 02 (Box 30, Folder 5)
  - 1894 Mar 03 - 1894 Mar 05 (Box 30, Folder 6)
  - 1894 Mar 06 - 1894 Mar 08 (Box 30, Folder 7)